

(214) 862-2529 m_abaya79@yahoo.com

www.myreille-abaya.design

Summary

I'm a UX/UI Designer and Developer with a background in film and TV production. I'm passionate about helping people experience the world better.

Projects

Sourcery

Recipe generator research | branding | visual design

BlocJams

Interactiive music player frontend development

PX

Cloud storage for photos and videos research | branding | visual design

References

Flower Hulihan

505-410-0284 flowerh@mac.com

Ilo Orleans

510-326-4361 adhocprod@gmail.com

Chris Smyth

972-655-4734 csmyth76@gmail.com

Work Experience

BEYOND FILMS, LUMINANCE WEDDING FILMS

Freelance Video Editor Mar. 2013 to Dec. 2017

AD HOC PRODUCTIONS.

Electronic Press Kit Writer Sept. 2012

"CAPITAL GAMES"

Assistant Editor
July to Aug. 2012

MAK PICTURES, MIKE MATHIS PRODUCTIONS

Script Coordinator / Transcriber Sept. 2011 to July 2012

FILM GARDEN ENTERTAINMENT.

Script Coordinator, Footage Coordinator, Transcriber / Logger

Jan. 2004 to Mar. 2011

SIRENA FILMS

Assistant Editor

Dec. 2004 to Dec. 2007.

Education

BLOC

UX Design and Frontend
Development Apprenticeship
Feb. 2019

LOYOLA MARYMOUNT UNIVERSITY

B.A. in Television Production High honors May 2002

Skills

UX Research Wireframing
Branding Prototyping
Visual Design Writing
User Testing
Info Architecture

Tools

Figma Adobe XD

Sketch Illustrator

Photoshop Final Cut Pro X

Adobe Premiere

HTML/CSS

Javascript/JQuery

Git, Github